[banner fluttering]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[growls]
[thunderclap]
Hmm.
[scoffs]
[ELYMAS] The Heavy Knight.
HEAVY KNIGHT
A densely armored class
that specializes in defense
and draws enemy attacks
to protect allies.
But compared to the many
other defensive classes,
it lacks versatility.
With its weak
offensive abilities,
leveling up
is almost impossible.
AS A RESULT
As a result,
it's considered to be
a truly unfortunate
and defective class.
[girl chuckles]
-[both breathing anxiously]
-[gulps]
-[all breathing anxiously]
-Huh?
[bell tolling in distance]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[both chuckle]
Hmm.
There's been a lot of talk
about this Raid Quest.
Apparently, a clown has chosen
to join us tonight.
Must be you, Elymas.
There are plenty
of novices like you
who completely underestimate
guilds and monsters.
-[all gasp]
-You managed to beat
an Ariandype at Level 12?
That means nothing to me!
Adventuring isn't so easy!
I'll teach you a lesson,
one you aren't ever
going to forget!
[strains quietly]
[growling]
[ELYMAS] Well, this sucks.
[♪ opening theme song playing]
EPISODE 3 THE RAID QUEST
[♪ ominous music playing]
[growling]
[strains quietly]
[ELYMAS] Well, this sucks.
But Raid Quests are
a rare chance at promotion.
Can't afford to miss this one.
So then...
I look forward
to working with you, sir.
[grunts]
Hmm.
Hmph! I don't like this,
but fine.
Okay, Teal, get to it then.
Of course, Mr. Gowtan.
Hmm.
[chuckles]
[grunts]
Search.
[ELYMAS] Search.
It detects creatures
in the surrounding area.
It's a rare skill
for a low-level adventurer.
[GOWTAN] Hmm.
[TEAL] Hmm.
There's a horde nearby.
Roughly 30 enemy undead.
Right.
That's some good work, Teal.
[TEAL] Yes, but with
my exceptional skill,
would you expect any less?
I'm hoping you're so impressed
you'll grant me that promotion
to E-rank.
-[scoffs]
-[Teal laughs]
And you.
Your bizarre, unusual behavior.
Well, it sparked
quite a number of rumors
at the guild about you, Elymas.
[ELYMAS] Judging by his dress
and equipment,
he must be a Red Mage.
They have strong
physical abilities,
they can cast attack
and healing spells,
and use a broad range
of support spells.
I feel bad for you
being in a defective class.
Your concern is appreciated.
That said, I'm actually
quite happy with this class.
[laughs]
Hmm.
[grunts, scoffs]
You think you're tough?
Well, just don't hold us back,
you hear?
[Elymas sighs] What's his deal?
If anything,
Red Mage is the more
challenging class.
At first glance,
they seem to be capable
of almost anything.
But in the game, they were known
as the typical
jack-of-all-trades type.
But this world isn't the game.
Naturally, people favor classes
that are easy to use.
Now everybody listen up!
This undead horde we're facing
has a leader. A Ghoul Head!
[ADVENTURER 1]
That's a strong monster.
As a D-rank adventurer,
the Ghoul Head's
my responsibility.
Yours is, stay out of my way
and fight the horde!
[ADVENTURER 1]
You won't protect us?
Not if you get caught
between me and my foe!
-[all gasp]
-Seriously?
[ADVENTURER 2]
I'm staying in the back.
So then, Mr. Gowtan is only
focusing on the boss?
[ADVENTURER 3] I thought we'd
just have to stand next to him.
-[growls]
-[ELYMAS] The Ghoul Head.
It's around Level 30.
It has no attack skills.
But its Hades Breath skill
that turns corpses
into low-level Wights
is a real pain.
On the plus side,
we have Gowtan.
A D-rank adventurer
who's around Level 40.
If things go smoothly,
I think we can win.
However...
[ADVENTURER 4] We're dead.
[ADVENTURER 5] We're definitely
going to die.
[ELYMAS] Cowardice.
[ADVENTURER 3]
This was a bad idea!
[TEAL] What weaklings.
[ADVENTURER 6] Pathetic cowards.
ARROGANCE
[ELYMAS] Arrogance.
I'm dealing with scared newbies
who thought raids would be easy,
and a careless leader
who won't look after his team.
The odds we'll survive
are only 80%.
That's decent for a game.
But in this world,
death is more
than just a setback.
-Gowtan.
-Hmm?
Shouldn't you be giving us
some instructions
that are more
detailed and specific?
[all gasp in disbelief]
What did you say?
The report
about the undead horde.
What if it isn't
completely accurate, sir?
It'll be far too late if we wait
for the worst to happen.
[growls]
[all gasp]
[ADVENTURER 2]
What is he saying?
Is he making a suggestion
to Gowtan?
[ADVENTURER 1] Is he insane?
[growls]
What? You're telling me
how to run a Raid Quest?!
[all gasp]
[both chuckle]
[growls]
-[ELYMAS] No.
-Hmm?
[ELYMAS] I'm just anxious
because unlike you,
I'm inexperienced and low-level.
[growls]
So are all of the others
here tonight.
For a veteran adventurer
like yourself,
this raid
might be business as usual.
[growls]
But we'd appreciate
more instructions.
[gasps sharply]
[Gowtan growls]
Hmm. I'm not your
damn babysitter, but fine!
[all sigh with relief]
-[TEAL] Hold up!
-[ALL] Huh?
We don't need instructions.
[Elymas sighs]
Maybe you would,
given your class,
but the rest of us aren't scared
of a few weak undead.
Crying to Gowtan already?
That's even before we faced
a single monster.
[sighs in annoyance]
[all whimper anxiously]
[GOWTAN] Hmm.
[chuckles gleefully]
Ignore this fool.
We don't need any more
instructions, Mr. Gowtan.
If there are more cowards
like Elymas,
stay out of our way
and run to the rear.
-Isn't that right, Mr. Gowtan?
-Hmm.
[gasps]
[Wights snarling]
-[all whimper anxiously]
-[TEAL] When did they get here?
[Wights snarling]
[GOWTAN] Hmm.
[gasping in terror]
[whimpering]
[gasps]
-[sword clinks]
-[grunts]
[grunts]
[growling]
[roars]
Ignore this fool.
We don't need any more
instructions, Mr. Gowtan.
If there are more cowards
like Elymas,
stay out of our way
and run to the rear.
-Isn't that right, Mr. Gowtan?
-Hmm.
[gasps]
[Wights snarling]
[all whimpering anxiously]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[GOWTAN] Hmm.
[gasping in terror]
[growling]
[whimpering]
[shrieks]
-[sword clinks]
-[grunts]
[grunts]
[growling]
[roars]
[yelps]
-[shrieks]
-Get back up!
-[both gasp]
-[GOWTAN] Teal! Paul!
-Clear the way for me now!
-[BOTH] What?
Follow my lead!
-[PAUL] Yes, sir!
-[grunts]
[whimpering]
[Wight snarling]
[snarling]
[growls]
[ELYMAS] Its club doesn't seem
to be anything special at all.
They should be fine.
[Wights snarling]
All right, guys.
Let's take care
of the Ghoul Head's followers.
[ALL] Huh?
Wait, you want us to charge
into all of those monsters?
[ADVENTURER 2]
What should we do?
Look, they may just be Wights,
but we're all dead meat
if they surround us.
I only came 'cause I thought
Mr. Gowtan was gonna
take them out for us!
I didn't know he was
gonna focus on the boss.
[ELYMAS] So that's it.
No wonder
they're so unmotivated.
[ADVENTURER 4]
You've gotta be kidding me.
[ELYMAS]
They're so inexperienced.
They've never faced
a monster horde before,
let alone creepy undead.
And without proper instructions,
I can understand
why they're so hesitant.
-[all whimpering anxiously]
-[sighs]
-[ELYMAS] Listen up.
-[ALL] Huh?
You'll form into
two teams of three.
-[ALL] Huh?
-If we start watching
each other's backs,
we can keep the Wights
from overwhelming us.
[both trembling]
-Hmm.
Fine. We'll do it.
But what about you?
Where will you be?
I'll be drawing undead
to me on the front line.
I'll buy time for you
to rally yourselves.
Look, you seem
to have some experience, friend,
but it's reckless
to do that alone.
[ADVENTURER 3] You won't be able
to heal fast enough.
And aside from all of that,
aren't you a slow Heavy Knight?
-[growls]
-Ah!
♪
-[Elymas grunts] Parry!
-[sword clangs]
[gasps]
[AUTOMATED VOICE] Skill: Parry.
Use a sword or shield
to deflect enemy attacks
and create openings.
[snarling]
[grunts]
[panting]
-[sword clangs]
-[grunts]
Parry! [panting]
[grunts] Parry!
[grunts]
Disarm!
[huffs]
[Wights snarling]
[grunts]
Rampart Reflection!
[Wights snarling]
RAMPART REFLECTION
[Wight growls]
[sighs]
[all gasping]
[ADVENTURER 1]
He did that by himself?
Don't worry.
It's a Heavy Knight's job
to attract enemy hordes.
Don't let your guards down.
And if you see anything strange,
tell the others.
I'll give what help I can.
-[ADVENTURER 1] What?
-[all gasping]
-[sword clanging]
-[monsters growling]
[sighs]
How's a defective class
taking out so many Wights alone?
Isn't he just an F-rank
Heavy Knight?
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Level 16 has been reached.
[ELYMAS] Good. Parry's working
even better than I expected.
And fighting this many enemies
at this level is efficient.
Display stats.
ELYMAS EDVAUGHN
ATTACK DEFENSE MAGIC SPEED
CLASS: HEAVY KNIGHT
[ELYMAS] Nice.
It's climbing steadily.
He said he was gonna
draw them all to himself,
but he's practically mowing
all of them down.
[ADVENTURER 3] I don't know
if we should stick
-behind him or not.
-[all chattering]
This guy's really strong,
but he's starting to scare me
more than the Wights.
[ELYMAS] Seriously?
[♪ adventurous music playing]
[grunts]
[both panting]
[Elymas grunts]
[cape rustling]
[sighs]
[ELYMAS] That's most of them.
[ADVENTURER 4] Um, Mr. Elymas,
should we go and help
Mr. Gowtan now?
The Ghoul Head?
It's a much higher level
than we are.
Let's leave it to Gowtan
to handle.
[panting]
[growling]
-[growls]
-[grunts]
[both grunting]
[grunts]
[yells]
[grunts, pants]
[growling]
[roars]
[grunts]
You still won't go down?
Stubborn monster!
-[grunts]
-[slashes]
Teal! Paul!
Draw more Wights to yourselves!
[whimpering in fright]
Why are you two
being such cowards?!
If you don't step up,
I won't give you that promotion!
Please understand, Mr. Gowtan.
If we get any closer
to the Ghoul Head,
and we get caught in the fight,
we're no good to you.
Besides,
we can assist from here. [gasps]
-[scoffs]
-[growls]
[grunts]
[yelling]
-[grunts]
-[slashes]
[GOWTAN] Rock Shatterer!
[groaning]
[both gasp]
-[all gasp]
-Yeah!
Display stats.
[Ghoul Head groaning]
MONSTER: GHOUL HEAD
[ELYMAS] All right.
With one more hit,
Gowtan could knock out
its remaining HP.
But still...
-[Wight snarls]
-[Gowtan gasps]
[both gasp]
-[Wights snarling]
-[grunts]
Those Wights are in the way.
[Teal, Paul whimpering]
Um, should we go
attack the Wights?
No, we wait here.
-[Ghoul Head growls]
-[gasps]
[all gasp]
[growls]
[chomping]
[grunts]
[Teal, Paul gasp]
-[Ghoul Head growls]
-[Gowtan gasps]
[growls]
[all whimpering]
[Ghoul Head growls]
[both whimpering]
-[chomping]
-[all whimpering]
[ADVENTURER 1] It healed?
The Consume Corpses skill.
It helps recover HP by eating
corpses and the undead.
There's a low chance
for Ghoul Heads to have it.
Still, that's odd.
Consume Corpses
shouldn't require it
to eat so many undead to heal.
This doesn't make sense.
Unless...
[gasps]
[grunts]
[roars]
[all gasp]
Could it be?
It may have healed,
but at least now all those
damnable Wights are gone.
[grunts]
Gowtan, stop!
Get away from that thing!
[Gowtan grunts] I'll settle this
once and for all!
[roars]
[all whimpering]
[both whimpering]
[gasps]
[roaring]
[grunting]
[roars]
[gasps]
What?!
[AUTOMATED VOICE] Ghoul Head
has evolved into Mad Headder.
Level 40 has been reached.
GHOUL HEAD HAS EVOLVED
INTO MAD HEADDER
[all gasp in horror]
[both whimpering]
[gasps]
-[Mad Headder roars]
-[breathing heavily]
[laughing]
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[ELYMAS] A rare monster
has leveled up,
and the situation
couldn't be worse.
After evolving, the Mad Headder
is now even more powerful
than the high-level Gowtan.
F-rank adventurers like us
are no match for it.
If I take a single direct hit,
I'll die.
Next time,
"Existence Evolution."
Even so, this kind of situation
really fires me up!